Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 54, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Your State University offers Services for Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: The institute of Management and Labor Relations Serves New Jersey, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations Educational Services for New jersey Business and Industry Offered By Management Program, Institute of Management and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: 24th Annual Rutgers AFL Labor Institute, 1954; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Education Conference: Independent Unions of New Jersey, Inc., 1954; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Films and Stripfilms for Labor Groups, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: How Free is Communication? - Convention Education Feature, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: The Hosiery Industry and the National Economy: An Educational Conference, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: You As Delegate, Consumer and Citizen: A Conference Sponsored by Telephone Workers' Union of New Jersey in Cooperation with Institute of Management and Labor Relations, Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey, 1952; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Services for Labor, 1954-1955 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Planning a Local Union Education Program, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: Serving New Jersey: Institute of Management and Labor Relations, 1959; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Education In Labor-Management Relations: A Rutgers Extension Program in Action, 1952; Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
    Author: Richard H. Wood
  - Item 15: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Box: 54, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Economic Controls In Our National Emergency: Summary of Conference, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Developing and Maintaining An Active Union: Third Annual Fall Conference, 1952; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Labor Program Yearly Report: General Comments; Extension Activities; Special Activities; Conclusions and Recommendations; Statistical Summary, 1953-1954 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: TA 09-147 - German Chemical-Textile Productivity Team, Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Labor Program Staff Conference: Evaluating the Fourth Year, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Conference on Workmen's Compensation, Safety and Education for New Jersey Local Unions, United Rubber Workers-CIO, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Fifth Annual Labor-Management Conference, 1953; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: State University Services for Labor: Consultation Service; Conferences; Discussions; Classes; Summer Schools, Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Education in Labor-Management Relations: A Rutgers Extension Program in Action, 1952; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Establishing A Training Program: Selected Experiences, 1953; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: District 4, IUE-CIO Leadership Institute in Cooperation with Institute of Management and Labor Relations, 1953; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: A Review of Activities of the Public Program, 1953-1954 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Work with Labor Groups: Institute of Management and Labor Relations Labor Program, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Box: 54, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Saco-Lowell Coaching System: On the Job Coaching Simplified, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
    Author: Albert F. Koepcke
  - Item 2: How Saco-Lowell Simplified the Problem of On-the-Job Coaching, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Saco-Lowell Coaching System: On the Job Coaching Simplified, Publication (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Box: 54, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Sage-Allen Plan, Publication (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Box: 54, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Courses of Instruction in Labor-Management Relations, 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Courses of Instruction in Labor-Management Relations: A Three Year Program, Publication (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Box: 54, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Payroll Employees and Groupo Life Insurance Plan of St. Joseph Lead Company, 1952; Publication (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Box: 55, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Safety Rules, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Medical Benefits, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Box: 55, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Employees of San Diego Gas & Electric Company, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Group Health Plan for Employees of the San Diego Gas & Electric Company, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Unemployment Compensation Disability Benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Savings Plan for Employees of San Diego Gas & Electric Company, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Retired Employees Hospital & Surgical Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Group Health Plan with Supplemental Major Medical Benefits for Employees of San Diego Gas & Electric Company, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Group Health Insurance Plan for Employees of San Diego Gas & Electric Company, 1966; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Pension Plan for Employees of San Diego Gas & Electric Company, 1966; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Servicemen & Their Debts, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Statement of Coverage: San Diego Gas & Electric Company Self-Insured Voluntary Plan of Unemployment Compensation Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Notice, 1953; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Personnel Department, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Box: 55, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention Rules, 1953; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Job Questionnaire, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Box: 55, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Group Insurance Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Author: Murray T. Parker
  - Item 2: Job Rights for Reservists and Guardsmen, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance: Life - Medical - Dental, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Box: 55, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Sangamo Electric Company Scholarship Award Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Application for Scholarship Award, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Sangamo Spells Security, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Measuring Your Job and Your Pay, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Employee Merit Rating Report, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Methods Analysis Chart, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Aids to Education via Santa Fe, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Box: 55, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Don't Move This Workman Until his Injuries Have Been Determined, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Never Reach Into Operating MachineryKeep Guards in Place, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: All Accidents Involve Hands, Eyes & Feet, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Newsletter, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Author: C.E. Scott
  - Item 5: Tumble Trouble, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Let's Keep Cool, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: If You Spill It Wipe It Up - prevent A Fall, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Start From Scratch: Report Even Minor Injuries for First Aid At Once - Delay May Mean Infection!, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Box: 55, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Method Improvement and Personal Development, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Author: J.R. Piechura
- Box: 55, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: From Profit Sharing to Common Ownership, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Box: 55, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Contribution Plan For Support of Higher Education, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Student Aid Plan, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Employees' Stock Purchase Plan for 1968 and Scott Paper Company Employees' Stock Investment Program - 1968 Class, 1967; Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Scott Paper Company Retirement Plan for Salary Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Salaried Employee Benefit Program: Your Key to Confident Living, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Box: 55, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Measuring the Job: Scott Salaried Job Evaluation Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Bridging the Gap from Campus to Industry, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Measuring the Job: Scott Salaried Job Evaluation Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Educational Refund Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Student Aid Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Educational Refund Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Highlights of your Scott Group Benefits Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: You Can Buy Scott Stock Two Ways, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Scott Paper Company Employees' Retirement Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Long-Term Disability Plan for Salaried Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Scott Paper Company Employees' Stock Purchase Plan for 1965 and Scott Paper Company Employees' Stock Investment Program - 1965 Class, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Box: 55, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Looking Forward to Retirement: A Service Program For All Employees to Help Take the Guesswork Out of Planning for the Leisure Years, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Box: 55, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Bulletin of the University of Scranton, 1956-1957 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Box: 55, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Joseph E. Seagram & Sons Inc. Industrial Education, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The Administration of Education Programs, 1948; Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
    Author: J. Manczyk
- Box: 55, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: From Generation To Generation: A Workable Program for Developing Young Executives, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Box: 55, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Looking Ahead at Sealed Power, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: To: Vice Presidents, 1955; Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Author: H.S.M. Burns
  - Item 3: Outline of Management Development, 1955; Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Box: 55, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Ninth Fortune Round Table, 1941; Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Box: 55, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Share Your Ideas: Sears Employee Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Your Military Leave, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: What We Have Learned from Operating Our Branch Stores In Mexico, Brazil, Venezuela, Colombia, Peru, Cuba, Canada and Australia, 1957; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Author: Theodore V. Houser
  - Item 4: The Sears Organization: Past and Present, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1954; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees: Rules and Regulations, 1969; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Your Military Leave, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Tips on Buying On Time - Sears Employee Information, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1953; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Plans, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Box: 55, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Quick Facts for Initial Training Of New Employees, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Sears Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Retirement from Sears, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Your Social Security Program, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Certificate of Group Hospital and Surgical Benefits for:, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: The Supplemental Savings and Retirement Plan of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations and Trust Agreement, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Plans, 1966; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Your Military Leave, 1966; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: The Supplemental Savings and Retirement Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Retiree Group Medicare Supplement Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Retiree Group Health Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: Your Statement of Hospital and Surgical Plan Benefits, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Your Military Leave, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 16: Retiree Group Hospital and Medical Expense Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 17: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: Your Statement of Hospital and Surgical Plan Benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 19: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 20: Retiree Group Hospital and Medical Expense Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 21: Your Military Leave, 1953; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 22: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 23: Group Life Insurance for Employees of Sears, Roebuck & Co., 1959; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 24: The Savings and Profit Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck & Co. Employees - Rules and Regulations, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 25: Group Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 26: Retiree Group Hospital and Medical Expense Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 27: Group Life Insurance for Sears, Roebuck & Co., 1956; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Box: 55, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Sears Medical Plan for Employees and Their Families, 1970; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Medical Coverage for Retirees and Dependents, 1970; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Your Military Leave, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Medical Plan for Employees and Their Families, 1970; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Group Life Insurance and Travel Accident Insurance, 1970; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: It's Your Move, 1970; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Sears, Roebuck in Latin America, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Sears and the Junior College Graduate, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Tips on Financing a College Education - Sears Employee Information, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Security for You, Through Sears Group Illness, Hospital and Surgical Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: The Retailer and the State, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
    Author: T.V. Houser
  - Item 12: Urban Renewal: Excerpts from an Address Given to the Better Business Bureau of Chicago, 1956; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
    Author: T.V> Houser
  - Item 13: Sears Invites you to Discuss Careers, 1969; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Opportunities in Data Processing Management at Sears, 1969; Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 15: The Sears Foundation Merit Scholarship Program for High School Seniors, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 16: The Retailer and the USA Economic Evolution, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Item 17: Sears Foundation Merit Scholarship Program for High School Seniors, Publication (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Box: 55, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Ordinance 56172, Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Index to Compensation Ordinance, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Box: 55, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Palm Sunday Storm Hits Midwest; Company Losses Heavy, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Box: 55, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: If You Have a Problem in Management, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Don't be a Dumb Bunny! - Unionism from A to Z for Union Workers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Union MenIt's Your Move! - Union Education: A program Available to All Workers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Human Relations are Here to Stay! - The Modern Approach to Labor-Management Problems; Twenty Courses in Industrial Relations for Alert men of Management, Publication (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Box: 56, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Sears National Personnel Department: Its Organization and Function, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Sears World, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Sears National Training: Getting Acquainted with Sears, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Sears and the College Man: An Invitation to Discuss Career Opportunities with Sears, Roebuck & CO., Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Sears and the College Man: An Invitation to Discuss Career Opportunities with Sears, Roebuck & Co., 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Sears National Training: Handbook for Getting Acquainted with Sears - Retail Basic Training, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Sears and the College Man: An Invitation to Discuss Career Opportunities with Sears, Roebuck & Co., 1964; Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Sears and the College Graduate: An Invitation to Discuss Career Opportunities with Sears, Roebuck & Co., 1966; Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Box: 56, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Required Training Manual, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Planned Training for Retail, 1955; Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Box: 56, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Sears Concept of Executive Development, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Author: C.B. Caldwell
  - Item 2: Successful Executive Leadership, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Sears Concept of Executive Development, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Needed: An Up-To-Date Yardstick for "Opportunity", Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Author: R.E. Barmeier
  - Item 5: Summary of Personnel Developments in the United States - 5th Period, 1952; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Wants and Needs - Where Policies Begin: A look at the Thinking Behind Our Personnel Program, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Author: W.W. Tudor
  - Item 7: Personnel Library, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The Study of Employee Attitudes and Morales - Fifth Annual Seminar Sponsored by the Office Management Association of Chicago and Northwestern University, 1947; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Author: James C. Worthy
  - Item 9: Acquisitions and Annotations: Personnel Library. 707, 1951; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Factors Contributing to High Morale Among Sears Employees, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Acquisitions and Annotations - Personnel Library. 707, 1951; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Factors Influencing Employee Morale - Reprinted from Harvard Business Review, 1950; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Training Materials Catalog, 1951; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Box: 56, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: We Think Sears Copywriters are the Best In the Business, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Catalog Sales Office Induction Training, 1974; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Catalog Sales Office Induction Training, 1974; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Retail Induction Training, 1972; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Parent Induction Training, 1972; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Catalog Order Induction Training, 1972; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Sears Parent News, 1967; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: This is my Sears Suggestion: Improve Merchandise; Improve Sales; Improve Service; Improve Safety; Reduce Expenses, 1963; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Sears and the College Graduate, 1971; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Career Opportunities and Training for Sears Service Technicians, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Sears and the College Graduate, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Getting Acquainted with Sears: Retail Induction Training, 1970; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Box: 56, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: An Investigation of the Dimensions of Executive Morale, 1958; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Induction Training Manual: Instructor's Guide for Training New Employees - Retail Training, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Management's Expanding Challenge in personnel Administration, 1957; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Sears Supplemental Pension Plan: Rules and Regulations and Trust Agreement, 1969; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Lifetime Income For The Years Ahead, 1969; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: It's Your Move, 1973; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Think Twice About Sears: A College Graduate's Guide to Management Careers That Are Tougher, More Rewarding, and More Diverse Than You'd Expect, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Sears National personnel Department: Its Organization and Function, 1954; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Handbook for Getting Acquainted with Sears: Retail Basic Training, 1958; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Savings and Profit-Sharing Pension Fund of Sears, Roebuck and Co. Employees: Descriptive Summary of Fund - 1963, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Sears and the College Man: An Invitation to Discuss Career Opportunities with Sears, Roebuck and Co., 1958; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)